To, The Head, Human Resource Department

Sub: Application for a suitable vacant position in the Human Resources function

Dear Sir,

My name is Sapna, working as HR & Administration Manager, with UV Asset Reconstruction Company Limited since November 2014, a known name in the list of ARC Industry.

From April 2014 to Oct 2014, I worked with Propetiger.com.

Prior to Proptiger.com, I was associated with ASF Insignia IT SEZ Pvt. Ltd. As Admin Executive.

I have also worked with Leisure Streak Hospitality Pvt. Ltd. as "Guest Relation Executive" for 2 years.

I have completed my 2 years Post Graduate Diploma program in Human Resource Management from IMT CDL Ghaziabad (2011-2013), Graduated in 2011 (B.com) from Delhi University.

Please go through my Curriculum Vitae for your kind perusal. Looking forward to a positive response.

With Best Regards,

Sapna

Sapna

Address: Mehrauli, New Delhi-110030

Contact Details: (M) 91-9654510377, 91-7678506444

E-Mail: me_sapnasharma@rediffmail.com

Seeking assignments in Human Resource Function with a growth-oriented organization offering Personal Development opportunities based on performance and thereby securing a challenging and rewarding position.

Key Strengths

- Formulating and streamlining organizing policies and processes
- Manpower handling and grievance management
- Balanced decision-making, thereby meeting employee as well as organization needs
- Dedicated and highly ambitious professional to achieve personal as well as organizational goals
- Maintaining effective business relationships for consistent success of the organization
- Adept at working in high pressure environments with deadlines and overlooking multiple deliverables
- Ability to work and participate in a team
- Strong willingness to learn & adapt new skills and abilities
- Excellent Communication and co-ordination skills

Employment Scan

Current Experience:

Manager HR & Administration – UV Asset Reconstruction Company Limited. 20th November, 2014 to till date

Key Responsibility Areas:

- ✓ Setting up HR policies, processes, procedures for all aspects of HR from recruitment to exit and looking after their implementation
- ✓ Conducting Employee Engagement activities and planning annual HR events
- ✓ Formalizing and updating attendance and payroll related systems
- ✓ Conducting trainings with and through employees on various disciplines
- ✓ Oversee End to End Lifecycle Management of an Employee Recruitment to Exit
- ✓ Designing Job descriptions for various positions and formalizing the current recruitment practices and processes
- ✓ Looking after manpower planning and setting up Key Responsibility areas for various teams and team members
- ✓ Handling employee grievances and constantly bridging the gap between employees and management
- ✓ Formalizing employee exit procedures, work out employee retention strategies and also helping employees by providing all necessary support and guidance

- ✓ Handling PF, ESI Gratuity, Medical Insurance & other compliances related to Labour laws.
- ✓ Travel Management (Air Tickets, Visa, Forex, Hotel Bookings)
- ✓ Day to day General Administration.
- ✓ Handling Petty Cash
- ✓ Vendor Management, Pantry Management & Housekeeping Management.

Past Experience:

Worked with Proptiger.com as a "HR and Admin Executive" from April 2014 to November 2014.

Worked with ASF Insignia SEZ Private Limited as "Admin Executive" from May 2013 to March 2014.

Worked with Leisure Streak Hospitality Pvt. Ltd. as "Guest Relation Executive" from May 2011 to April 2013

Academic Qualifications

- ✓ 2 Years Post Graduation Diploma in Human Resource Management from IMT CDL Ghaziabad.
- ✓ Graduate in Bachelor of Commerce (B. Com) from Delhi University.

Trainings Attended

- ✓ One Year Advance Certificate in Computer Education from Servants of the People Society.
- ✓ Certificate in Course on Computer Concepts (CCC) from DOEACC.

Personal Details

Date of Birth : 07th March 1991

Nationality : Indian Marital Status : Married

Languages Known: English & Hindi

References

Available on request